RG 169:007, Connecticut Forest and Park Association
Connecticut State Library
- Series 8. Publications, circa 1883-2011
  - Project Learning Tree publications, 1998-2007 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Pre K-8 Environmental Education Activity Guide. Washington, D.C.: American Forest Foundation, 2007
  - Proposed: A Plan of Conservation and Development for Connecticut. Hartford: Connecticut Office of State Planning, 1973 January (Box 26)
  - Broderick, Steve. Protecting Family Lands: A Starter kit for Farm and Forest Owners in the Quinebaug-Shetucket National Heritage Corridor, undated (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Buttrick, Philip Laurance, M.F. Public and Semi-Public Lands of Connecticut. Bulletin No. 49. Hartford: State of Connecticut State Geological and Natural History Survey, 1930; 2 duplicate copies (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Phillips, John C. and Thomas D. Cabot. Quick-Water and Smooth: A Canoeist's Guide to New England Rivers. Brattleboro: Stephen Daye Press, 1935 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Report of the Connecticut State Board of Fisheries and Game. Public document number 19. Hartford: State of Connecticut, 1938-1946 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    Includes the twenty-third biennial report and the twenty-sixth biennial report.
  - Report of the Commission on Forests and Wild Life. Public document number 81. Hartford: State of Connecticut, 1925-1945 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    Includes 2 duplicate copies of the report for fiscal years, July 1, 1925-June 30, 1930 and 2 duplicate copies of the report for fifteen years July 1, 1930-June 30, 1945.
  - Report of the Connecticut State Parks and Forests. Public document number 60. Hartford: State of Connecticut, 1928-1934 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    Includes report for fiscal year July 1, 1928-June 30, 1930; 2 duplicate copies of the tenth biennial report for fiscal years July 1, 1930-June 30, 1932; and 2 duplicate copies of the eleventh biennial report for fiscal years July 1, 1932-June 30, 1934.
  - Report of the Special Commission on Taxation of Woodland to the General Assembly of 1913. Hartford: State of Connecticut, 1912 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Filley, Walter O. Report of the Connecticut Agricultural Experiment Station, Eighth Report of the State Forester, 1915, Being Part III of the Annual Report (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Reports of the State Park and Forest Commission, 1922-1944 (Box 19, Folder 16-19)
  - Suttie, Roscoe Henry, C.E. Report on the Water Resources of Connecticut. Bulletin No. 44. Hartford: State of Connecticut State Geological and Natural History Survey, 1928 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Woolsey, Theodore S., Jr. Riding the Chuck Line: A Forester in Peace and War. New Haven: The Tuttle, Morehouse & Taylor Company, 1930 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Rocks and Minerals of Connecticut. Miscellaneous series number 1. Hartford: State Geological and Natural History Survey of Connecticut, 1949 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Rounding Out the Giant: The First Opportunity in Several Years for Substantial Progress Toward Completing the Sleeping Giant State Park. New Haven: Sleeping Giant Park Association, Inc., 1940 May; 10 duplicate copies (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Sanctuary. Newsletter of the White Memorial Conservation Center. Vol. XXI, no. 4, 2003-2004 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Pack, Charles Lathrop. The School Book of Forestry. Washington, D.C.: The American Tree Association, 1922 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Frothingham, Earl H. Second-Growth Hardwoods in Connecticut. U.S. Department of Agriculture, Forest Service bulletin 96. Washington: Government Printing Office, 1912 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Chapman, H. H. Shall Our State Parks be Self Supporting? Publication number 38. New Haven: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1938 May (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Comey, Arthur C. Ski Trail Standards. Reprinted from Appalachia, Vol. XIX, number 3. New England Trail Conference publication number 22, 1933 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - The Sleeping Giant. New Haven: Sleeping Giant Park Association, Inc., 1928 July; 4 duplicate copies (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Smith, David M. publications, 1976-1977 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Changes in Eastern Forests Since 1600 and Possible Effects. Chapter 1 reprinted from Perspectives in Forest Entomology. New York: Academic Press, Inc., 1976
    - The Scientific Basis for Timber Harvesting Practices. Reprinted from J. Wash. Acad. Sci. Vol. 67, no. 1, 1977
  - Moore, Adam R. So You Have Open Space...Now What?, 2003 December 4 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Morgan, M. F. The Soil Characteristics of Connecticut Land Types. Bulletin 423. New Haven: Connecticut Agricultural Experiment Station, 1939 May (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Bates, C. G. and O. R. Zeasman. Soil Erosion - a local and national problem. Research bulletin 99. Madison, WI: Agricultural Experiment Station of the University of Wisconsin, 1930 August (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Special Message from the President of the United States Transmitting A Report of the National Conservation Commission with Accompanying Papers. 60th Congress, 2nd Session, document number 676. Washington: Government Printing Office, 1909 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Hawes, Austin F. The State Forests of Connecticut and What They Are For. Hartford: State Forester, 1934 June (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - State Geological and Natural History Survey of Connecticut List of Publications, 1957 January 1 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - State Park Commission reports, 1915-1921 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - State Parks for Connecticut. A Reprint of the Report of the State Park Commission to the General Assembly. Public document number 60. Hartford: State of Connecticut, 1915
    - Report of the State Park Commission to the Governor for the Two Fiscal Years Ended September 30, 1918. Public document number 60. Hartford: State of Connecticut
    - Connecticut State Parks. A Reprint of the Report of the State Park Commission to the Governor. Public document number 60. Hartford: State of Connecticut, 1918
    - Connecticut State Parks. A Reprint of the Report of the State Park Commission to the Governor. Public document number 60. Hartford: State of Connecticut, 1921; 2 duplicate copies
  - State Park and Forest Commission. State Park Growth Use and Cost Studies, circa 1943 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Roosevelt, Theodore. Stories of the Great West. New York: The Century Co., 1917 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Streamlines. Connecticut's United Voice for River Conservation. Litchfield, CT: River Alliance of Connecticut, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Supplement to the Connecticut Walk Book. Wallingford, CT: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 1957 August (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Bentley, William R., ed. Sustaining Working Woodlands in an Urbanizing Environment. Proceedings from First Connecticut Forest Conservation Forum. The University of Connecticut West Hartford Campus, 2005 November 30 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Texas Forestry 75th Anniversary Issue. Vol. 30, no. 10. Lufkin, TX: Texas Forestry Association, 1989 October (Box 26)
  - Trails Guide Training Note Book, undated (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Carpenter, Edwin D. Trees and Shrubs for Connecticut. Storrs, CT: Cooperative Extension Service, College of Agriculture, University of Connecticut, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Trees in your community: A Handbook of Selected for New England. Second edition, undated; 2 duplicate copies (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Lull, Richard Swann. Triassic Life of the Connecticut Valley. Bulletin number 24. Hartford: State of Connecticut State Geological and Natural History Survey, 1915 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - United States Department of Agriculture publications, 1912-1986 (Box 20, Folder 22-23)
    - Benson, A. O. Dimension-Stock Methods for New England Hardwoods. Circular number 394. Washington, D.C.: U.S. Government Printing Office, 1936 August
    - Reynolds, R. V. and Albert H. Pierson. Fuel Wood Used in the United States 1630-1930. Circular number 641. Washington, D.C.: U.S. Government Printing Office, 1942 February
    - Influences of Vegetation and Watershed Treatment on Run-Off, Silting, and Stream Flow: A Progress Report of Research. Miscellaneous publication number 397. Washington, D.C.: U.S. Government Printing Office, 1940 July
    - Know Your Watersheds. Leaflet number 282, former AIS number 67. Washington, D.C.: U.S. Government Printing Office, 1953
    - Log Rule and Lumber Scale, undated
    - Benson, A. O. Manufacture of Dimension Stock from Northern Hardwoods. Circular number 163. Washington, D.C.: U.S. Government Printing Office, 1931 April
    - Randall, Charles E. Our Forest Resources: What They Are and What They Mean to Us. Agriculture information bulletin number 131. Washington, D.C.: U.S. Government Printing Office, 1954 November
    - Protecting the Forests from Fire. Agriculture information bulletin number 130. Washington, D.C.: U.S. Government Printing Office, 1954 December
    - Frothingham, Earl H. Second-Growth Hardwoods in Connecticut. U.S. Department of Agriculture, Forest Service bulletin 96. Washington: Government Printing Office, 1912
    - Soil Catenas of Connecticut, 1986
    - Phillips, John C. Wild Birds Introduced or Transplanted in North America. Technical bulletin number 61. Washington, D.C.: U.S. Government Printing Office, 1928 April
  - The Urban Setting: Man's Need for Open Space. A Symposium at Connecticut College, New London, Connecticut, March 28-29, 1980. New London, CT: Program in Human Ecology, Connecticut College, 1981 January; 3 duplicate copies (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Fletcher, E.D. and Austin F. Hawes. The Use of Lumber and Wood in Connecticut, 1928 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Vacation Week-End and One-Day Hiking Trips. Ho-Ho Kus, NJ: The Hiking Trips Bureau, 1937 May-October (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Grace, James R. Vegetation Management of Wetland Forests of Northeastern Connecticut. Hartford: Connecticut Department of Environmental Protection, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Carpenter, Edwin D. Vines for Connecticut. Storrs, CT: Cooperative Extension Service, College of Agriculture, University of Connecticut, undated (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - WalkConnecticut Family Hike Leaders' Handbook. Connecticut Forest and Park Association, circa 2007 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Longwell, Chester R. and Edward S. Dana. Walks and Rides in Central Connecticut and Massachusetts. New Haven: The Tuttle, Morehouse & Taylor Company, 1932 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Westfield Residents Association, Inc. News. Vol. 22, no 3., 2005 April (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Wheeler, Girard, B.S. The West Wall of the New England Triassic Lowland. Bulletin number 58. Hartford: State of Connecticut State Geological and Natural History Survey, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Hicock, Henry W. Wood and the Energy Crisis. Cheshire Herald, 1974 January-February (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Brett, Richard M. A Woodlot Primer. Reprint from American Forests. Washington, D.C.: The American Forestry Association, 1957 February (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Graves, Henry Solon. The Woodsman's Handbook. Part I revised edition. U.S. Dept. of Agriculture, Bureau of Forestry bulletin number 36. Washington: Government Printing Office, 1903; 2 duplicate copies (Box 20, Folder 34)
    Folder also contains a revised and enlarged edition from 1910.
  - Hawes, Austin F. The Work of a Forest Protective Association. Hartford: State Forester, 1924 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Yale Forest School News. Vol. 48, no. 2. New Haven: Yale Forest School Alumni Association, 1960 April (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Yale University School of Forestry Bulletins, 1925-1945 (Box 20, Folder 37-38)
    - Hawley, Ralph C. and Harold J. Lutz. Establishment, Development, and Management of Conifer Plantations in the Eli Whitney Forest, New Haven, Connecticut. Bulletin number 53. New Haven: Yale University, 1943
    - Hawley, Ralph C. and Robert T. Clapp. Growing of White Pine on the Yale Forest Near Keene, New Hampshire. Bulletin number 48. New Haven: Yale University, 1942
    - Hawley, Ralph C. and Rogers G. Wheaton. Studies of Connecticut Hardwoods. The Form of Hardwoods and Volume Tables on a Form Quotient Basis. Bulletin number 17. New Haven: Yale University, 1926
    - Leffelman, Louis J. and Ralph C. Hawley. Studies of Connecticut Hardwoods. The Treatment of Advance Growth Arising as a Result of Thinnings and Shelterwood Cuttings. Bulletin number 15. New Haven: Yale University, 1925; 2 duplicate copies
    - Meyer, Walter H. and Basil A. Plusnin. The Yale Forest in Tolland and Windham Counties, Connecticut. Bulletin number 55. New Haven: Yale University, 1945
- Series 9. Press Files, 1898-2010
  - Clippings, circa 1933-1974 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, 1985-2011 (Box 21, Folder 2-36)
  - Clippings, 1997-2003 (Box 26)
  - Clippings regarding Connecticut Forestry Association meetings, 1898-1903 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Connecticut Agricultural Experiment Station, 1951-2007 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Environmental Merit Awards, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Hawes, Austin F. obituary, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - News release, 2005 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Obituaries, 1991-2005 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - 100th Anniversary programs, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Press releases, 1955-2003, undated (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Programs, 1910-2010 (Box 22, Folder 9-14)
    Folders include programs, clippings, flyers, "Forces of Nature" program, and reports of annual meetings.
  - Riversplash '98 program, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Trails Day event brochure, 1999 June 5; An uncut rolled sheet what appears to be a printers proof. (Box 49)
  - Trails Day event brochures, 2000-2007 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Series 10. Legislative Files, 1921-2009
  - Agenda for State Action, 1980-2000 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Cape Cod National Seashore Zoning Standards, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Connecticut Environmental Briefing Book. Hartford: Connecticut League of Conservation Voters, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Environmental Agenda. Rockfall, CT: Connecticut Forest and Park Association, 2006 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Environmental Scorecard. Hartford: Connecticut League of Conservation Voters, 2004-2006 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Income Tax proposals, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Legislation, 2005-2006 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Legislative correspondence, 2001-2009 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Legislative papers, 1921-1949 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Legislative papers, 1964-2009, undated (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Proposed legislation, 1921 February 1 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Statements, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Testimony, 1992-2007 (Box 22, Folder 29)
- Series 11. Shaker Pines Corporation Files, 1937-1942
  - Correspondence, 1937-1942 (Box 22, Folder 30-31)
  - Capital stock shares book, 1937-1940 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Records, 1937-1942 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    Records include financial records, certificates, minutes, reports, and correspondence.
- Series 12. Photographs, 1900-2011
  - State Parks and Forests, 1920-2007
    - Bigelow State Forest workshop, 1997 October 4 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Goodwin State Forest, 1964 November 18-1966 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Great Mountain Forest, circa 1970 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Yale Forest, thinned white pines, Eastford, Connecticut, 1970-1999 April (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Yale Forest, Tour of Yale Forest with D. M. Smith, 1999 November 13 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Black Rock State Park, undated (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Devil's Hopyard State Park, 1997 May; Photographs of the falls. (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Dinosaur State Park, circa 1970 (Box 33, Folder 8)
      Folder consists of a reprint from Guide book number 2.
    - Gillette Castle, State Parks kick-off, 1995 May 26 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Hammonasset State Park, dune stabilization, circa 1970 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Harkness estate, 1952 April 25 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Harkness Mansion rededication, 1998 June 19 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Friends of Harkness State Park, 1995 September (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Harkness State Park, circa 1970 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - State Parks initiative presentation, undated (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Kettletown State Park, Southbury, undated (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Macedonia Brook State Park, 1996-1997; Bridge work on Salmon Trail. (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Macedonia State Park, 2007 April 24; Volunteers. (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Mohawk Ski Area, circa 1968 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Photos of State Parks, 1964-1996 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Postcards of Hammonasset and Devil's Hopyard, circa 1920 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Putnam State Park rededication, 1997 May 22 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Rocky Neck, undated (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Sherwood Island, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Sleeping Giant, Mount Carmel, Hamden, 1930 November 18-1988 (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Talcott Mountain acquisition, dedication and Hueblein, circa 1960-1969; Also includes a publication "Save Talcott Mountain," a campaign for aid to help the state purchase the property jointly sponsored by the Farmington River Watershed Association. (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Trash, undated (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - West Rock Ridge, undated (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - Trails, 1900-2011
    - Appalachian, Cornwall bridge, 1984-2000 August 4; Handicapped access built by Dick Blake. (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - Trail at the Arboretum, Connecticut College, New London, undated (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - Bear Mountain, Salisbury, 1900-1996 (Box 33, Folder 31)
    - Bigelow Hollow precutting logs, 2003 April 16 (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - Blaze new section, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 33)
    - Blue Blazed Trail, hiker resting, 1988 June (Box 33, Folder 34)
    - Blue Trails, 1998; Couple walked 400 miles of Blue Trails. (Box 33, Folder 35)
    - Blue Trail hiking, Mettabesett, Appalachian Trails, 1958-1977 (Box 33, Folder 36)
    - Bluff Point, circa 1990 (Box 33, Folder 37)
    - Brookfield bridge, 1989 August 10-1998 (Box 33, Folder 38)
    - Case Mountain, circa 1990 (Box 33, Folder 39)
    - Damage, undated (Box 33, Folder 40)
    - Hikers, 1988 June-1990 June (Box 33, Folder 41)
    - John R. Camp, 1999 December; Handicapped accessible trails construction. (Box 33, Folder 42-43)
    - Laurel Marsh Trail, undated (Box 33, Folder 44)
    - Maintenance, 1992-1994 June (Box 33, Folder 45)
    - Maintenance, Brookfield walkway, 1998 April-May (Box 33, Folder 46)
    - Maintenance, Charles L. Trail, circa 1992 (Box 33, Folder 47)
    - Maintenance, Kids Trail, 1988 August (Box 33, Folder 48)
    - Maintenance, Mohawk Trail, Cornwall, Connecticut, 1992-2002 (Box 33, Folder 49)
    - Maintenance, Shenipsit Trail, 1998 (Box 33, Folder 50)
    - Maintenance, two different trails, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 51)
    - Mattabesett Trail, 2011 June (Box 33, Folder 52)
    - Mattatuck Trail, Leatherman's Cave, 1991 September 28 (Box 33, Folder 53)
    - Metacomet Ridge Conservation Compact, 1998 April (Box 33, Folder 54)
    - Metacomet Trail, undated (Box 33, Folder 55)
    - Metacomet Trail construction, 1992 April (Box 33, Folder 56)
    - Metacomet Trail relocation at the McClean Game Refuge, 2003 January 8; Photographs show The Rovers working on the trail. (Box 33, Folder 57)
    - Metacomet Trails, circa 2004 (Box 33, Folder 58)
    - Mohawk Mountain, 1991 March 17 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Mohawk Trail, 2000 March; Work party, photographs by Dave Boone. (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Natchaug, Mount Higby, circa 1980 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Nipmuck, bridge at Mansfield Hollow, 1999 November-December (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Nipmuck Trail, Timberlands and Northern Nipmuck in Bigelow State Park, circa 1995; Ridge Trail and West Pond Trail. (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Old Blue Hills Road and Cherry Lane, undated (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Pachaug, Boardwalk Project, Rhododendron Sanctuary, 1998 May 21-1999 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Pachaug, Tunxis, workshop, Civilian Conservation Corps (CCC) Camp Wolcott, 1992 October (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Paugussett Trail, all terrain vehicle (ATV) damage, 2005 October 27 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Paugussett, Webb Mountain Park, Appalachian Mountain Club (AMC) and New Haven Hiking Club (NHHC) hike, 1985 October 27 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Poland Brook, Terryville (Plymouth), 1990 December; Falls called Upper Pond. (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Pomeraug Trail maintenance, 1996 April (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Quinnipiac River, Linear Trail, 1998 August 6; Folder includes an unplublished article. (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Ragged Mountain Preserve Loop to 372, Metacomet, rock climbers, 2006 December 5 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Rhododendrum Sanctuary and Boardwalk, construction of boardwalk, 1998; Folder also includes photographs of a meeting at headquarters. (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Roving Trail Crew at headquarters, 2000 September 27 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Roving Trail Crew at HSM, 2004 April (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Schoolhouse Brook Park, 1992 July (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Shenipsit Trail bridge construction by NELO Bike Club, 1993 March (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Sheipsit Trail extension, 1992 July (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Still River bridge and Blue Trail relocation, 1989 July-August (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Trails, six different trails, 1987-1999; Photographs possibly used for publications or exhibits. (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Trail abuse, undated; Photographs by Jerry Stage. (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Tunxis, Mile of Ledges, 1987; Photographs by Linda Rapp. (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Tunxis Trail volunteers, 1996; Photographs by Dan Casey. (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Vernal Pool Wetlands, undated (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - Vernon bicycles, undated (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - Zoar Appalachian Mountain Club (AMC) hike, 1994 April (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - Programs, 1905-2003
    - Trails Day, 1993-2003
      - National Trails Day, Ragged Mountain, undated (Box 34, Folder 29)
      - Charter Oak Landing and Ride-with-the-Blind, West Hartford Reservor's Bike Trail, 1998 June 6 (Box 34, Folder 30)
      - Cheshire event, 1996 June 1; Photographs by Bob Davis. (Box 34, Folder 31)
      - Fenton River Trails, 2000 June 3 (Box 34, Folder 32)
      - Gay City hike, 1993 June (Box 34, Folder 33)
      - Gay City State Park, 1994 June; Photographs by Duffy. (Box 34, Folder 34)
      - Hammonasset River Hike, Madison, 1998 June 6 (Box 34, Folder 35)
      - Horse riding, 1996 June 1-2003; Photographs by Bob Blaverstock. (Box 34, Folder 36)
      - Trails Day, John's Trails Day photos, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 37)
      - Killingworth hike, 1998 June 6 (Box 34, Folder 38)
      - Laurel Run hike and Whitehouse/Shenipsit, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 39)
      - Mattabesett Trail, 1998; Photographs by Ann Colsen. (Box 34, Folder 40)
      - Nayantaquit Trail, Nehantic State Forest, Lyme, 1994 June 4 (Box 34, Folder 41)
      - New Milford, Housatanic Riverbelt Greenway, 1996 June 1; Photographs by Linda Therrien and Linda Rapp. (Box 34, Folder 42)
      - Nipmuck Trail, Mansfield, 2003 June 3 (Box 34, Folder 43)
      - Trails Day with photo captions of various locations, 1999 June 5; Locations include: Torrington. Photographs by Art Talmadge, Gabe Piwonski, Sam Langley, and Kent Heidenis. (Box 34, Folder 44)
      - Peoples Forest, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 45)
      - Pomperaug dedication, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 46)
      - Pomperaug Trail, Oxford, 2002 June 1; Photographs by Peter Petrochko. (Box 34, Folder 47)
      - Salmon Trail, 1994 June 4-2003 June 7; Photographs by C. Brooks. (Box 34, Folder 48)
      - Shenipsit Lake, CWC tour, 1996; Photographs by Linda Therrien. (Box 34, Folder 49)
      - Shenipsit Loop, Glastonbury, 1999; Photographs by Duffy Schade. (Box 34, Folder 50)
      - Sleepy Giant State Park, Hike A Giant, 1999 June 16 (Box 34, Folder 51)
      - Stratton Brook and Windsor Locks Canal, Releaf and others, awards, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 52)
      - Participants at Stratton Brook State Park, Simsbury, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 53)
      - Torrington and Guida Farm Conservation Area, 1998 June 8; Led by Sam Langley. (Box 35, Folder 1)